Earn a higher degree in terror!
Splatter University is a horror, mystery, thriller
film directed by Richard W. Haines.
A sociology instructor finds her new teaching duties at a private
college interrupted by the presence of a killer.
Julie Parker, played by Forbes Riley.
Mark Hammond, played by Ric Randig.
Father Janson / Daniel Grayham, played by Dick Biel.
Cathy Hunter, played by Kathy Lacommare.
Mrs. Bloom, played by Mary Ellen David.
Cynthia, played by Laura Gold.
Splatter University is a 1984 American slasher film directed by Richard W.
Haines and written by Haines alongside Michael
Cunningham and John Elias Michalakis.
It was distributed by Troma Entertainment.
The film explores themes of college, knife, murder, rampage, serial killer.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.